American Society for Biochemistry and Molecular Biology records
American Society for Biochemistry and Molecular Biology records
- Series IV. Meetings, 1906-2002; bulk 1934-2002; 29 boxes (42.35 linear feet)
  - Subseries IV.G. International Congress of Biochemistry (ICB), 1952-1991; bulk 1961-1982; 152 folders
    - Sixth, 1964, Publications Correspondence, 1962-66 (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - Sixth, 1964, Registration Correspondence, 1962-63 (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - Meetings ICB Sixth, 1964, Registration Correspondence (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - Sixth, 1964, Requests for Congress Announcements (Box 90, Folder 18)
    - Sixth, 1964, Sub. Allow. Apps. Summary (Box 90, Folder 19)
    - Sixth, 1964, Sub. Allow. Apps., Argentina, Australia, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Canada, Chile (Box 90, Folder 20)
    - Sixth, 1964, Sub. Allow. Apps., Czechoslovaki (Box 90, Folder 21)
    - Sixth, 1964, Sub. Allow. Apps., Denmark, Egypt (Box 90, Folder 22)
    - Sixth, 1964, Sub. Allow. Apps., England (Box 90, Folder 23)
    - Sixth, 1964, Sub. Allow. Apps., Ethiopia, Finland, Formosa (Taiwan) (Box 90, Folder 24)
    - Sixth, 1964, Sub. Allow. Apps., France (Box 90, Folder 25)
    - Sixth, 1964, Sub. Allow. Apps., Germany (Box 90, Folder 26)
    - Sixth, 1964, Sub. Allow. Apps., Greece, Hungary, India, Iran, Iraq, Ireland, Israel (Box 90, Folder 27)
    - Sixth, 1964, Sub. Allow. Apps., Italy (Box 90, Folder 28)
    - Sixth, 1964, Sub. Allow. Apps., Jamaica (Box 90, Folder 29)
    - Sixth, 1964, Sub. Allow. Apps., Japan (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Sixth, 1964, Sub. Allow. Apps., Lebanon, Mexico (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Meetings ICB Sixth, 1964, Sub. Allow. Apps., Netherlands (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Sixth, 1964, Sub. Allow. Apps., New Zealand, Nigeria, Norway, Pakistan, Peru, Portugal, Republic of South Africa, Republic of the Congo (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Sixth, 1964, Sub. Allow. Apps., Scotland, Spain, Sudan, Sweden, Switzerland (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Sixth, 1964, Sub. Allow. Apps., Syria, Uganda, Uruguay, U.S.S.R., Wales (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Sixth, 1964, Sub. Allow. Awards for Symposium Speakers (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Sixth, 1964, Subsistence Allowance/Travel Grant Correspondence, 1962-64 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Sixth, 1964, Translation Committee (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Sixth, New York, 1964, U. S. National Committee, Budget (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Sixth, 1964, Visa Correspondence: Britain,Czechoslovakia, Germany, Hungary, Poland, Russia (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Sixth, 1964, Visa Correspondence on Specific Individuals (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Sixth, 1964, Visa General Correspondence, 1963-65 (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Sixth, 1964, Visa Sidney Shall (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - Seventh, 1967, Abstracts I (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - Seventh, 1967, Abstracts II (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - Seventh, 1967, Abstracts III (Box 91, Folder 17)
    - Seventh, 1967, Abstracts IV (Box 91, Folder 18)
    - Seventh, 1967, Abstracts V (Box 91, Folder 19)
    - Seventh, 1967, Abstracts, Supplement I and Author Index (Box 91, Folder 20)
    - Seventh, 1967, Announcements (Box 91, Folder 21)
    - Seventh, 1967, Charter Flights (Box 91, Folder 22)
    - Seventh, 1967, Chevy Chase Travel (Box 91, Folder 23)
    - Seventh, 1967, General Correspondence (Box 91, Folder 24)
    - Seventh, 1967, General Correspondence (Box 91, Folder 25)
    - Seventh, 1967, List of Participants (Box 91, Folder 26)
    - Seventh, 1967, Plenary Lectures (Box 91, Folder 27)
    - Seventh, 1967, Proceedings Copy 1 (Box 91, Folder 28)
    - Seventh, 1967, Proceedings Copy 2 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Seventh, 1967, Proceedings Copy 3 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Seventh, 1967, Program Correspondence (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Seventh, 1967, Programs (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Seventh, 1967, Speakers from the USA (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Seventh, 1967, Translations (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Seventh, 1967, Travel Committee Correspondence (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Seventh, 1967, Travel Grant Awardees (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Eighth, 1970, Bloch, Konrad, Correspondence, 1968-70 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Eighth, 1970, Charter Flight Arrangements, Chevy Chase Travel (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Eighth, 1970, Charter Flight Proposals (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Eighth, 1970, General Correspondence (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Eighth, 1970, General Correspondence, Jan-April (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - Eighth, 1970, General Correspondence, May-Dec (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - Eighth, 1970, Members/ Mailings (Box 92, Folder 15)
    - Eighth, 1970, Organizing Committee Correspondence (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - Eighth, 1970, Programs (Box 92, Folder 17)
    - Eighth, 1970, Report of Highlights (Box 92, Folder 18)
    - Eighth, 1970, Travel Award Program, List of Applicants (Box 92, Folder 19)
    - Eighth, 1970, Travel Committee Correspondence (Box 92, Folder 20)
    - Eighth, 1970, Travel Committee Meeting Minutes and Miscellaneous Materials (Box 92, Folder 21)
    - Eighth, 1970, Travel Grant Awardees (Box 92, Folder 22)
    - Ninth, 1973, General Correspondence (Box 92, Folder 23)
    - Ninth, 1973, General Correspondence (Box 92, Folder 24)
    - Ninth, 1973, General Correspondence, Jan-May (Box 92, Folder 25)
    - Ninth, 1973, General Correspondence June-Dec (Box 92, Folder 26)
    - Ninth, 1973, General Correspondence (Box 92, Folder 27)
    - Ninth, 1973, Grant Correspondence (Box 92, Folder 28)
    - Ninth, 1973, International Union of Biochemistry (IUB) Mailings/ Member Mailings (Box 92, Folder 29)
    - Ninth, 1973, Statutes/ By- Laws of the IUB (Box 92, Folder 30)
    - Ninth, 1973, Stockholm Alcohol and Aldehyde Symp. Grant (Box 92, Folder 31)
    - Ninth, 1973, Travel Award Committee Correspondence (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Ninth, 1973, Travel Grant Awardees Applications, A-B (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Ninth, 1973, Travel Grant Awardees Applications, C-F (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Ninth, 1973, Travel Grant Awardees Applications, G-J (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Ninth, 1973, Travel Grant Awardees Applications, K-L (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Ninth, 1973, Travel Grant Awardees Applications, M-O (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Ninth, 1973, Travel Grant Awardees Applications, P-R (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Ninth, 1973, Travel Grant Awardees Applications, S-T (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Ninth, 1973, Travel Grant Awardees Applications, V-Z (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Tenth, 1976, Brochures on Hamburg, Germany (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Tenth, 1976, General Correspondence, Jan-March (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Tenth, 1976, General Correspondence, April-May (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Tenth, 1976, General Correspondence, June-Dec (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Tenth, 1976, Hamburg Reception (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Tenth, 1976, Invited Speakers (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - Tenth, 1976, NSF-NIH Grants (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - Tenth, 1976, Travel Award Committee Correspondence (Box 93, Folder 17)
    - Tenth, 1976, Travel Awardees, A-D (Box 93, Folder 18)
    - Tenth, 1976, Travel Awardees, E-J (Box 93, Folder 19)
    - Tenth, 1976, Travel Awardees, K-N (Box 93, Folder 20)
    - Tenth, 1976, Travel Awardees, O-R (Box 93, Folder 21)
    - Tenth, 1976, Travel Awardees, S-W (Box 93, Folder 22)
    - Tenth, 1976, Travel Grant Correspondence (Box 93, Folder 23)
    - Tenth, 1976, Travel Grant Correspondence (Box 93, Folder 24)
    - Eleventh, 1979, General Correspondence (Box 93, Folder 25)
    - Eleventh, 1979, General Correspondence (Box 93, Folder 26)
    - Eleventh, 1979, Programs (Box 93, Folder 27)
    - Twelfth, 1982, Circulars (Box 93, Folder 28)
    - Twelfth, 1982, General Correspondence (Box 93, Folder 29)
    - Twelfth, 1982, General Correspondence (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Twelfth, 1982, Grant Application Materials (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Twelfth, 1982, Grant Application, Public Health Service (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Twelfth, 1982, Grant Applications (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Twelfth, 1982, Grant Correspondence (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Twelfth, 1982, Information on Australia (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Twelfth, 1982, Reception (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Twelfth, 1982, Request for Funds (Meister) (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Twelfth, 1982, Transportation (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Twelfth, 1982, Travel Award Committee Correspondence (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Twelfth, 1982, Travel Awardees, A-J (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Twelfth, 1982, Travel Awardees, K-M (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - Twelfth, 1982, Travel Awardees, N-S (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - Twelfth, 1982, Travel Awardees, T-Z (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - Twelfth, 1982, Travel Awards, Withdrawn (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - Thirteenth, 1985, 2nd I International Meeting on Metallothionein (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - Subseries IV.H. Gordon Research Conference, 1953-1976; 18 folders
    - Correspondence (GRC) (1983) and slide of the attendees at the first Gordon Conference (1953) (Box 94, Folder 17)
    - 1954, 1956, 1957, 1958, 1960 (Box 94, Folder 18)
    - 1961 Abstracts (Box 94, Folder 19)
    - 1961, Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 94, Folder 20)
    - 1961, Correspondence, Jan-March 1961 (Box 94, Folder 21)
    - 1961, Correspondence, April-Nov 1961 (Box 94, Folder 22)
    - Attendance Records, 1962-68 (Box 94, Folder 23)
    - 1962 (Box 94, Folder 24)
    - 1962, Conference on Food and Nutrition (Box 94, Folder 25)
    - 1963, 1964 (Box 94, Folder 26)
    - 1965, 1966, 1967 (Box 94, Folder 27)
    - 1968 (Box 94, Folder 28)
    - 1969 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - 1969, Chairman (Harte) Correspondence (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - 1969, Chairman (Harte) Correspondence (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - 1969, Workbook Materials (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - 1970, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - 1974, 1976 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Subseries I.I. Miscellaneous Meetings and Conferences, 1951-1991; bulk 1961-1982; 5 folders
    - Travel, Committee on Travel Awards, 1956-59 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - BioMed '76, Correspondence, 1974-75 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - BioMed '76, Correspondence, 1976-77 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - BioMed '78, Correspondence (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - 17th FEBS Meeting, Berlin 1986 (Box 95, Folder 11)
- Series V. Affiliated Organizations, 1933-2002; bulk 1946-1991; 14 boxes (19.65 linear feet)
  - Subseries V.A. Affiliated Organizations A-B, 1954-1989
    - Academic Alliances (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Advisory Committee for Scientific Publications (1st meeting) 1963 (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - Advisory Committee for Scientific Publications (2nd meeting) 1963 (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - Advisory Council of College Chemistry (Box 95, Folder 15)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) Correspondence 1954-1962 (Box 95, Folder 16)
    - AAAS Correspondence 1963-1968 (Box 95, Folder 17)
    - AAAS Minutes/ Annual Reports 1969 (Box 95, Folder 18)
    - AAAS Correspondence/ Reports 1969-1970 (Box 95, Folder 19)
    - AAAS Minutes/Reports 1971 (Box 95, Folder 20)
    - AAAS Minutes/Reports 1972 (Box 95, Folder 21)
    - AAAS Minutes/Reports 1973 (Box 95, Folder 22)
    - AAAS Minutes/Reports 1974-1975 (Box 95, Folder 23)
    - AAAS Minutes/Reports 1976 (Box 95, Folder 24)
    - AAAS Minutes/Reports 1977-1979 (Box 95, Folder 25)
    - AAAS Minutes/Reports 1980-1982 (Box 95, Folder 26)
    - AAAS Minutes/Reports 1985-1987 (Box 95, Folder 27)
    - AAAS Minutes/Reports 1988-1991 (Box 95, Folder 28)
    - AAAS Bulletins 1966-1971 (Box 95, Folder 29)
    - American Association of Immunologists 1977-1989 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - American Association of Pathologists (AAP) 1984-1990 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - American Biology Council, 1970-1971 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - American Chemical Society (ACS) (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - ACS Division of Biological Chemistry Committee 1956-1962 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - ACS Council Meeting 9-13-1960 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - ACS Council Meeting 4-10-1960 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - ACS Council 1960-1963 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - ACS Committee on Publications 1963 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - ACS Annual Reports 1961, 1963 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - ACS Committee on Publications 1962-1963 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - ACS Council Minutes/Reports 1963-1964 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - ACS Division of Biological Chemistry 1963-1967 (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - ACS Committee on Publications 1964 (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - ACS Division of Chemical Literature 1964 (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - ACS Committee on Publications 1965 (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - ACS General Correspondence 1965-1967 (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - ACS Committee on Publications 1966 (Box 96, Folder 18)
    - ACS Division of Biological Chemistry 1966-1967 (Box 96, Folder 19)
    - ACS Annual Reports 1966-1969 (Box 96, Folder 20)
    - ACS Spring Meeting 1968 (Box 96, Folder 21)
    - ACS Fall Meeting 1968 (Box 96, Folder 22)
    - ACS General Correspondence 1969-1970 (Box 96, Folder 23)
    - ACS General Correspondence 1971-1973 (Box 96, Folder 24)
    - ACS General Correspondence 1974-1976 (Box 96, Folder 25)
    - ACS General Correspondence 1977-1979 (Box 96, Folder 26)
    - American Documentation Institute 1960-61 (Box 96, Folder 27)
    - American Institute of Biological Sciences Congress 1970-1973 (Box 96, Folder 28)
    - American Institute of Nutrition 1960-1977 (Box 96, Folder 29)
    - American Medical Association 1959-1960 (Box 96, Folder 30)
    - American Petroleum Institute 1959-1960 (Box 96, Folder 31)
    - American Physiological Society 1984-1987 (Box 96, Folder 32)
    - American Society for Cell Biology (Box 96, Folder 33)
    - American Type Culture Collection (ATCC) (Box 96, Folder 34)
    - Association for Accreditation of Human Research Protection Programs (AAHRPP) (Box 96, Folder 35)
    - Association of American Medical Colleges (AAMC) 1967 (Box 96, Folder 36)
    - AAMC Reports 1967-1968 (Box 96, Folder 37)
    - AAMC Correspondence 1968-1970 (Box 96, Folder 38)
    - AAMC General Correspondence 1971 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - AAMC Newsletters 1971 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - AAMC General Correspondence 1971 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - AAMC General Correspondence 1971 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - AAMC General Correspondence 1972 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - AAMC General Correspondence 1973 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - AAMC General Correspondence 1974 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - AAMC Meeting Agendas 1974 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - AAMC General Correspondence 1975 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - AAMC Annual Reports 1975 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - AAMC Council of Teaching Hospitals Survey 1976 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - AAMC Memorandums/Reports 1976 (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - AAMC Assembly Reports/ Agendas 1976 (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - AAMC General Correspondence 1977 (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - AAMC General Correspondence 1978-1980 (Box 97, Folder 15)
    - AAMC General Correspondence 1985 (Box 97, Folder 16)
    - AAMC General Correspondence 1986 (Box 97, Folder 17)
    - AAMC General Correspondence 1987 (Box 97, Folder 18)
    - AAMC General Correspondence 1988 (Box 97, Folder 19)
    - AAMC General Correspondence 1989-1990 (Box 97, Folder 20)
    - Association of Medical School Departments of Biochemistry (Box 97, Folder 21)
    - Association of Medical School Departments of Biochemistry (Box 97, Folder 22)
    - ASCB Denver Hotel Controversy 1985-1987 (Box 97, Folder 23)
    - ASCB Testimony on Biomedical Research Training 1989 (Box 97, Folder 24)
    - Biomedical Communications Study Section; Research Grant Proposals 1969 (Box 97, Folder 25)
    - Biomedical Communications Study Section; Research Grant Proposals 1969 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Biomedical Communications Study Section; Research Grant Proposals 1969 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Biochemical Society Correspondence 1970 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Subseries V.B. Affiliated Organizations C, 1962-1991; 57 folders
    - Chemical Abstract Service (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Chemical Rubber Company 1968-1970 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Council of Biology Editors (CBE) Conferences 1962-1964 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - CBE Correspondence/Minutes 1964-1965 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - CBE Correspondence/Minutes 1966 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - CBE Correspondence/Minutes 1967 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - CBE Correspondence/Minutes 1964-1968 (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - CBE Meetings 1969 (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - CBE Correspondence/Minutes (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - CBE Correspondence/Minutes (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - CBE Committee of Editors of Biological Journals (CEBJ) 1969-1972 (Box 98, Folder 14)
    - CBE European Life Sciences Editors (ELSE) Council 1970 (Box 98, Folder 15)
    - CBE General Assembly EAEBP 1970 (Box 98, Folder 16)
    - CBE Correspondence/Minutes (Box 98, Folder 17)
    - CBE Ontario Meeting 1970 (Box 98, Folder 18)
    - CBE American National Standards Institute (ANSI), Committee on Z39 1970 (Box 98, Folder 19)
    - CBE Handbook of Journal Economics 1970-1972 (Box 98, Folder 20)
    - CBE Nominating Committee 1970-1974 (Box 98, Folder 21)
    - CBE Meetings 1971 (Box 98, Folder 22)
    - CBE Correspondence/Minutes 1971 (Box 98, Folder 23)
    - CBE Correspondence/Minutes 1972 (Box 98, Folder 24)
    - CBE ANSI Committee on Z39 1972-1973 (Box 98, Folder 25)
    - CBE Correspondence 1973-1977 (Box 98, Folder 26)
    - CBE ANSI Committee on Z39 1974-1977 (Box 98, Folder 27)
    - CBE CEBJ 1974-1979 (Box 98, Folder 28)
    - Council of Scientific Society Presidents (Box 98, Folder 29)
    - Dwight D. Eisenhower National Mathematic and Science Education Program (Box 98, Folder 30)
    - Council of Engineering & Science Society Executives (CESSE) 1980 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - CESSE 1981 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - CESSE 1982 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - CESSE Annual Meeting 1984 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - CESSE 1985 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - CESSE Convention Liaison Council (CLC) 1985-1986 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - CESSE Annual Meeting 1987 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - CESSE CLC 1987 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - CESSE Annual Meeting 1988 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - CESSE CLC 1988 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - CESSE 1989 (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - CESSE 1990-1991 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - CESSE CLC 1991 (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - Council of Scientific Society Presidents (CSSP) General 1973-1974 (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - CSSP General 1975-1976 (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - CSSP General 1979 (Box 99, Folder 16)
    - CSSP Meeting Minutes 1980 (Box 99, Folder 17)
    - CSSP General 1980 (Box 99, Folder 18)
    - CSSP General 1981 (Box 99, Folder 19)
    - CSSP General 1982 (Box 99, Folder 20)
    - CSSP General 1983, 1985 (Box 99, Folder 21)
    - CSSP General 1986-1987 (Box 99, Folder 22)
    - CSSP General 1988-1991 (Box 99, Folder 23)
    - The Center for History of Chemistry 1985-1991 (Box 99, Folder 24)
    - Chemical Abstracts Service 1957-1961 (Box 99, Folder 25)
    - Committee for Health and Research (Box 99, Folder 26)
    - Council of Academic Societies (Box 99, Folder 27)
    - CRC Handbook of Biochemistry 1968-1970 (Box 99, Folder 28)
    - Cohn, Waldo 1970-1972 (Box 99, Folder 29)
    - Creationism 1981-1982 (Box 99, Folder 30)
  - Subseries V.C. Affiliated Organizations D-H, 1960-1973; 9 folders
    - Estabrook, Robert W. Correspondence 1971 (Box 99, Folder 31)
    - Estabrook, Robert W. Correspondence 1972-1973 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Federal Support to Science 1964-1966 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Food Nutrition Board 1960-1962 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Food Nutrition Board 1963-1965 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Garvey, William D. of the Center for Research in Scientific Communication (CRSC) (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Garvey, William D. CRSC (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Harte, Robert, Drafts/Complete "Molecules in Three Dimensions" (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - H.R. Bill 8809, 1969, Office of Science Information Services, NSF (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Subseries V.D. Federation of American Societies for Experimental Biology (FASEB), 1933-1990, 2001; 201 folders
    - FASEB Executive Committee 1933-1946 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - FASEB Control Committee "Rules for Handling Copy" 1941-1943 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - FASEB Proceedings Correspondence 1947-1950 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - FASEB Executive Committee 1947-1950 (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - FASEB Proceedings Correspondence 1948-1951 (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - FASEB Special Report on FASEB-ASBC 1950-1951 (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - FASEB Executive Committee 1950-1952 (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - FASEB Executive Committee 1950-1952 (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - FASEB Constitution and Bylaws 1952 (Box 100, Folder 17)
    - FASEB Proceedings 1953-1961 (Box 100, Folder 18)
    - FASEB Secretaries Committee 1953-1957 (Box 100, Folder 19)
    - FASEB Board Correspondence 1953-1961 (Box 100, Folder 20)
    - FASEB Headquarters Committee 1955-1958 (Box 100, Folder 21)
    - FASEB "Procedure for Centralized Billing of Membership Dues" 1956 (Box 100, Folder 22)
    - FASEB "Biochemistry-Nutrition Smoker" 1958-1960 (Box 100, Folder 23)
    - FASEB Secretaries Committee Meeting 1959 (Box 100, Folder 24)
    - FASEB Advisory Committee Correspondence 1959-1961 (Box 100, Folder 25)
    - FASEB Board Minutes 1959-1969 (Box 100, Folder 26)
    - FASEB Secretaries Committee Minutes 1959-1960 (Box 100, Folder 27)
    - FASEB Symposia Correspondence 1960-1962 (Box 100, Folder 28)
    - FASEB Secretaries Committee 1960-1965 (Box 100, Folder 29)
    - FASEB "Science Manpower Commission" 1961-1967 (Box 100, Folder 30)
    - FASEB Annual Meeting 1962-1964 (Box 100, Folder 31)
    - FASEB Symposia Correspondence 1962-1963 (Box 100, Folder 32)
    - FASEB Advisory Committee 1962-1964 (Box 100, Folder 33)
    - FASEB Annual Meeting 1963 (Box 100, Folder 34)
    - FASEB Executive Committee 1965-1968 (Box 100, Folder 35)
    - FASEB Ad Hoc Beaumont House Committee 1965-1967 (Box 100, Folder 36)
    - FASEB Editorial Committee 1966-1970 (Box 100, Folder 37)
    - FASEB and American Institutes for Research AIR) Proposal 1966 (Box 100, Folder 38)
    - FASEB Directory Correspondence 1966 (Box 100, Folder 39)
    - FASEB Executive Committee Minutes/Bylaws and Proposed Plans 1966 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - FASEB Ad Hoc Committee on Closed Circuit TV 1966-1967 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - FASEB Exhibits/Advisory Committee 1967 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - FASEB Committee on Revision of Questionnaire 1967 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - FASEB Committee on Revision of Questionnaire 1967 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - FASEB Editorial Committee Minutes 1967-1968 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - FASEB Executive Committee Meeting 6/22/1968 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - FASEB Executive Committee Meeting 9/23/1968 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - FASEB Annual Meeting 1968 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - FASEB Correspondence with Sidney B. Colowick 1968-1970 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - FASEB Public Affairs Committee 1968 (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - FASEB Public Information Committee 1968 (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - FASEB Executive Committee Meeting 2/1968 (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - FASEB Correspondence with Dr.'s Stanford Moore and J.A. McManus 1968-1970 (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - FASEB Cosmo Club Correspondence 1969-1977 (Box 101, Folder 15)
    - FASEB R.H. Grant Correspondence 1969 (Box 101, Folder 16)
    - FASEB Long Range Planning Committee 1969 (Box 101, Folder 17)
    - FASEB Executive Committee Meeting/Minutes 1969 (Box 101, Folder 18)
    - FASEB Public Affairs Committee 1969 (Box 101, Folder 19)
    - FASEB Publications Committee 1970 (Box 101, Folder 20)
    - FASEB William D. Garvey Grant Proposal Review 1970 (Box 101, Folder 21)
    - FASEB Executive Committee1970-1971 (Box 101, Folder 22)
    - FASEB House Committee 1970 (Box 101, Folder 23)
    - FASEB Meetings Committee 1970 (Box 101, Folder 24)
    - FASEB Public Affairs Committee 1970 (Box 101, Folder 25)
    - FASEB Programs Committee 1970, 1971 (Box 101, Folder 26)
    - FASEB Federation Board 1970-1972 (Box 101, Folder 27)
    - FASEB Editorial Board 1971, 1984 (Box 101, Folder 28)
    - FASEB Public Affairs Committee 1971 (Box 101, Folder 29)
    - FASEB Executive Committee 1971 (Box 101, Folder 30)